A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, John D., III (John Davison) (1906-1978)
Rockefeller, David (1915-2017)
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman (1910-2004)
Mauze, Abby Rockefeller (1903-1976)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) (1908-1979)
FA094
635.31 Cubic Feet 1657 containers - 1589 letter document boxes, 66 legal document boxes, 1 legal tall box, and 1 half-letter box.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research in accordance with the terms of donation from the David Rockefeller Estate, January 2019. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Arrangement
Original order. Alphabetical, primarily by subject/topic.
Scope and Contents
The 1962-1976 general files chronicle management of the philanthropic affairs of the third generation of the Rockefeller family primarily Abby Rockefeller Mauze, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller, and David Rockefeller.
Over the years the Rockefeller family has been involved in virtually all aspects of modern philanthropy at the local, national and international levels through their foundation activities as well as their individual personal giving. Major interests include: physical and mental health, conservation, education, international relations, politics, population, religion, social welfare, the visual and performing arts, cultural exchange programs, and economic and social development of underdeveloped areas.
The general files primarily consist of correspondence, reports, pamphlets, memoranda, charters and certificates of incorporation, minutes and meeting records as well as documentation of contributions, finance and investment materials, real estate, newspaper clippings, diaries, notebooks, calendars, audio tapes, and printed material.
Related Materials
FA1502 Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1996, Index Cards, RG 3-RG 44.
Westchester County (N.Y.); Agriculture; Charities -- Investments; Education; Economics; Philanthropy -- New York (State); Political science; Philanthropy -- United States; Philanthropy; Philanthropy -- New York (N.Y.); Charities; Charitable contributions; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Richford (N.Y.); Race and society; Environmental sciences; North Dakota; Race relations; Illinois; Arts; Cemeteries; Energy; International relations
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3; 636.07 Cubic Feet 1659 containers - 1591 letter document boxes, 66 legal document boxes, 1 legal tall box, and 1 half-letter box.
  - A, 1962-1976; 1; 3.42 Cubic Feet 9 letter document boxes
    - A Miscellaneous - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - A Miscellaneous - Advertising Council, 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - A Miscellaneous - Aldrich, Winthrop W., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - A Miscellaneous - Arnold, Stanley N., 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
    - Agriculture - Center for Rural Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Agriculture - Foreign - International Institute for Rural Reconstruction, 1962-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Agriculture - National Farm Workers Service Center, Inc., 1962-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Agriculture - National Farm Workers Service Center, Inc. - Contributions (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Agriculture - New Communities, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - A-I, 1962-1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - J-Z, 1962-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - Articles (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - Contributions (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
    - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - IRI Research Institute (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - IRI Research Institute - Articles (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Applicants - A-C, 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
    - Applicants - D-H, 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
    - Applicants - I-M, 1962-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
    - Applicants - N-S, 1962-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
    - Applicants - T-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts, 1962-1976; 2; 49.46 Cubic Feet 129 letter document boxes and 1 legal document box
    - Arts - A-Z, 1
      - Arts - A-Am, 1962-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
      - Arts - An-Cn, 1962-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
      - Arts - Co-H, 1962-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
      - Arts - I-L, 1962-1976 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
      - Arts - M-Na, 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
      - Arts - Nb-P, 1962-1976 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
      - Arts - L. Outhwaite - Study of Cultural Institutions and Government (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Arts - L. Outhwaite - Study of Cultural Institutions and Government (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Arts - L. Outhwaite - Study of Cultural Institutions and Government - Europe (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Arts - L. Outhwaite - Museums and the Future (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Arts - Q-R, 1962-1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Arts - S-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
      - American Crafts Council - Shaker Film, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - American Crafts Council, 1964-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - American Friends of Canada, 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - American Institute of Architects, 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Arkansas Art Center, 1962-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
      - Arkansas Art Center - Public Affairs - Clurman, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Arkansas Art Center - Contributions, 1962-1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Arkansas Art Center - Fund Raising, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Arts Councils of America, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts - Advocates for the Arts, 1972-1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts - General - A-Z (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts - Partnership for the Arts, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts - Contributions, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Associated Councils of the Arts - Printed Material, 1967-1976 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - General, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - A-Z, 1967-1976 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - Aspen Conference, 1967 May (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - Contributions, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - Finances, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - Meetings/Minutes, 1966-1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - Printed Material, 1967-1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - Members, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Business Committee for the Arts - Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Center for the Arts at Ithaca, 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Century Association - A-L, 1962-1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Century Association, 1962-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Children's Art Carnival, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Committee to Rescue Italian Art, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Conference on Arts and Young People, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Island Center of St. Croix, Ltd., 1966-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Council for the Arts in Westchester, 1973-1976 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Cultural League of New York, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Inter-American Foundation for the Arts, 1964-1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - International Association of Plastic Arts, 1962-1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Jackson Hole Fine Arts Foundation, 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1967-1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - General - A-H, 1956-1976 (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - General - I-R, 1956-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Aims and Purpose, 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - General - S-Z, 1956-1976 (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Annual Report, 1959-1972 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Applicants, 1963-1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Appreciation, 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Articles, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Building Costs, 1958-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Printed Matter (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Board of Directors, 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Board of Directors, 1956-1966 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - By-laws, 1956-1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Clippings, 1962-1969 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Constituent Relations, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Miscellaneous) - A-Z, 1958-1972 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Federation of Economic Organizations, 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Mrs. Vincent Astor, 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Mr. & Mrs. John F. Bryce, 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Vivian B. Allen Foundation, Inc., 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Confidential, 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Corporate Giving, 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Shelby Cullom Davis, 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - French Government, 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - John A. Hartford Foundation, Inc., 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Arthur A. Houghton, Jr., 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Albert A. List, 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Rockefeller Family Members, 1962-1967 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Mrs. C. Ruxton Love, Jr., 1958-1972 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Stavros S. Niarchos (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Colonel S. Vanderbilt (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Vanderbilt, Harold S., 1958-1972 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Wien, Lawrence A., 1958-1972 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1958-1972 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Diary Notes, 1955-1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Employees, 1965-1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Employee Benefits Plan, 1962-1969 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Film Committee and Department, 1966-1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Film Society, 1972-1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Finances, 1963-1976 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fund Raising, 1969-1976 (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising, 1967-1968 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising, 1963-1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Individuals - A-Z (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Committee for the Performing Arts at Lincoln Center, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Corporate Support, 1967-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Colonel Henry Crown, 1954-1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Mrs. Josephine H. Graeber, 1961-1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - John Paul Getty, 1960-1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Juilliard (John D. Rockefeller 3rd Kit), 1968 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Joseph Kennedy Memorial Foundation, 1960-1966 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Labor, 1964-1969 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Gustave L. Levy, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Development Committee Meetings/Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Lincoln Center Fund Meetings/Minutes, 1965-1970 (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Furnishings and Art Objects, 1966-1970 (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Juilliard School of Music, 1964-1972 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Juilliard School of Music - Chamber Music Society, 1967-1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Land Acquisition, 1964-1968 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Legal, 1959-1964 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Library Museum, 1963-1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Library Museum - Toscanini Memorial Archive, 1964-1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Lincoln Center Student Program, 1966-1969 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Meetings/Minutes Board of Directors, 1956-1976 (Box 42, Folder 6-7, Box 43, Folder 1-5, Box 44, Folder 1-4, Box 45, Folder 1-2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Meetings/Minutes Building Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 45, Folder 3-4, Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Meetings/Minutes Executive Committee, 1961-1971 (Box 46, Folder 2-3, Box 47, Folder 1-3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Meetings/Minutes Lincoln Center Council, 1966-1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Memos, 1969-1971 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - New York City - Relationship, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Metropolitan Opera, 1966-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - New York City - Arts Council, 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - New York Shakespeare Festival, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - New York State Theater, 1964-1971 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Philharmonic Hall, 1962-1970 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Policy Planning, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Printed Material, 1956-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2-4, Box 50, Folder 1-3, Box 51, Folder 1-2)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Releases, 1964-1971 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - The Repertory Theater of L.C. (Vivian Beaumont Theater), 1964-1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - William Schuman, 1961-1970 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Municipal Art Society of New York, 1964-1966 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Mountain Artisans, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - National Council on the Arts - National Endowment for the Arts, 1962-1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - National Endowment for the Arts - Printed Matter (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - New York State Council on the Arts (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Partnership for the Arts, 1970-1972 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Royal Society of the Arts, London, 1966-1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - New York State Council on the Arts - Printed Material (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - New York State Council on the Arts (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - San Francisco Art Institute, 1966-1971 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Saratoga Performing Arts Center, Inc., 1962-1976 (Box 55, Folder 2-3, Box 56, Folder 1-2)
      - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Clippings, 1963-1965 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Finances/Fund Raising, 1967-1971 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Fund Raising, 1963-1966 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Printed Material, 1964-1969 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Minutes/Meetings, 1967-1976 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Public Affairs, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Sunrise, Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Dance, 2
      - Dance A-M, 1962-1976 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
      - Dance N-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Ballet Theatre Foundation, Inc., 1962-1976 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Exhibitions, 3
      - Expeditions, 1962-1971 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Films, 4
      - Films A-Z, 1972-1976 (Box 59, Folder 1-4)
      - United Productions, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Furnishings, 5
      - Furnishings, 1962-1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Galleries, 6
      - Galleries A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 60, Folder 3, Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Libraries, 7
      - Libraries - A-K, 1962-1976 (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
      - Libraries - L-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1967-1976 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - New York Public Library, 1967-1976 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Pierpont Morgan Library, 1962-1976 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Seal Harbor Library, 1962-1971 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Memorials, 8
      - Memorials A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
    - Museums, 9
      - Museums - A-F, 1962-1976 (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
      - Museums - G-M, 1962-1976 (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
      - Museums - M-N, 1962-1976 (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
      - Museums - O-S, 1962-1976 (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
      - Museums - T-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Air Force Museum Foundation, Inc., 1962-1971 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - American Museum in Britain, 1962-1976 (Box 68, Folder 3, Box 69, Folder 1)
      - American Association of Museums, 1962-1976 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - American Museum of Immigration, 1962-1966 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - American Museum of Natural History, 1962-1976 (Box 69, Folder 3-4)
      - American Museum of Natural History - Boone and Crockett Club (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - American Museum of Natural History - Printed Material (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Bernice P. Bishop Museum, 1962-1975 (Box 70, Folder 3, Box 71, Folder 1-2)
      - Brooklyn Museum, 1962-1971 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Council on Museum Education, 1972-1973 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Dutch National Museum, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - The Frick Collection, 1967-1976 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - (Thomas) Gilgrease Institute of American History and Art, 1964 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - (Solomon R.) Guggenheim Museum, 1973-1976 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Institute of Contemporary Art, 1972-1976 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Israel Museum, 1965-1976 (Box 72, Folder 5, Box 73, Folder 1-2, Box 74, Folder 1)
      - (Louis) Leakey Memorial Institute for African Pre-History, 1971-1976 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Marine Historical Association, Inc., 1963-1966 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Board of Trustees (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - By Laws (Box 75, Folder 1)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Clippings (Box 75, Folder 2)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Cloisters (Box 75, Folder 3)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Contributions (Rockefeller Family) (Box 75, Folder 4-5)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Printed Material (Box 75, Folder 6, Box 76, Folder 1-3)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art - Rockefeller Wing (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Museum of African Art, 1964-1974 (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Museum of American Folk Art, 1962-1975 (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Museum of the American Indian (NY), 1971-1976 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Museum of the City of New York, 1973-1976 (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Box 78, Folder 2-3)
      - Museum of Modern Art - A-D (Box 79, Folder 1-2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - E-I (Box 80, Folder 1-3)
      - Museum of Modern Art - J-P (Box 81, Folder 1-3)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Q-Z (Box 82, Folder 1-2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Ad Hoc Planning Committee (Box 82, Folder 3, Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Mr. & Mrs. Alfred Barr, Jr. Party - The Playhouse, Pocantico Hills, 1967 June 22 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Board of Trustees - A-L (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Board of Trustees - M-Z (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Nominating Committee (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Carnival - General Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Carnival - Contributions, 1972-1976 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Clippings, 1972-1976 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Committee on Painting and Sculpture, 1972-1974 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions (Miscellaneous) (Box 85, Folder 2)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions - Rockefeller family - Cousins, 1962-1976 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions - Rockefeller family (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Museum of Modern Art - Contributions - Rockefeller, David, 1962-1976 (Box 85, Folder 5, Box 86, Folder 1-3)